List

<h2>More Facts About Dreams</h2>


<ul style="list-style-type:circle; text-align: left; padding-left: 10px; padding-right: 10px;">

	<li>Dreams actually occur most nights</li>

	<li>Dreams, while strange, are more than often related to our lives, as they are composed of things that are most important to us</li>

	<li>Most of the time, you have difficulty remembering your dreams</li>

	<li>While dreaming, you are sleeping so deeply that it is not possible to read or tell the time while dreaming</li>

	<li>Many great ideas have come from dreaming, including Google, sewing machine and the alternatic current generator (Tesla)</li>

	<li>People who have mastered the art of lucid dreaming are said to be able to fly, pass through walls, go back in time and even enter alternate dimensions</li>

	<li>Dreams have been rumored to hint at the future, and although it may just be a coincidence, Abraham Lincoln had a dream of him getting assassinated and people who were part of the 9/11 catastrophe had dreams warning them about it</li>

	<li>Sleepwalking has been known to be very dangerous. In fact, one man, while dreaming, walked to his car, drove 22 kilometres to his cousin's house, and then killed him, all while still asleep</li>

	<li>While dreaming, our brains are more active tham while you are awake</li>

	<li>You may think that you never dream, but that's not correct. Everyone dreams, but up to 60% of people aren't able to remember their dreams</li>

	<li>In dreams, you only see faces that you've seen in real like</li>

	<li>It is possible to have up to seven dreams in a single night</li>

	<li>In a man's dreams, 70% of people are male, but in a woman's dreams there is an equal ratio of genders</li>

	<li>12% of people aren't able to dream in colour, and only dream in black and white</li>

	<li>Over your lifetime, you will spend approximately six years dreaming</li>

	<li>90% of the memory of your dream is lost the minute you wake up</li>

	<li>It's not possible to dream while snoring</li>

	<li>People who suffer from sleep paralysis hear sounds and see people in their room while dreaming, as a result of the "fight, flight or freeze" behaviours of a human</li>

	<li>The colder your house, the more nightmares you will have</li>

</ul>

