What


<h2>

What are dreams?

</h2>

<p>

Dreams are a series of images and sensations experienced during sleep. A dream can last a few seconds or 20-30 minutes, A person is more likely to remember their dream of they are awakened during the REM (Rapid Eye Movement)  stage of their sleep which is about 2 hours of the 8 that a person is asleep. Dreams are often bizarre and strange containing events that the dreamer recognises. The dreamer is unaware that they are dreaming except when they are ‘lucid dreaming’ this means that the dreamer is aware that they are dreaming and in extreme cases can even control the dream. Dreams have been a subject of philosophical and religious interest throughout history. During REM sleep, the release of the neurotransmitters norepinephrine, serotonin and histamine is completely suppressed.

</p>