Why

 <h2>Why do dreams occur?</h2>

<p>

There is no scientifically, proven understanding of why dreams occur, but there are many theories. Those include improving your ability to remember things, the ability to regulate your emotions, a way to prepare yourself and have the knowledge to respond to threatening situations, just being a chemical process that is the result of other things happening in our brain while we sleep and for processing your memories of the past and present and using those memories to prepare yourself for the future.

</p>